https://eslpwr.com/terms-of-use/

Terms of Use - ESL Power Systems, Inc.
Copyright protection
All contents of www.eslpwr.com (‘this Website’) are protected by copyright. All users of this Website are bound to all terms and conditions found within. You are permitted to use this Website for your own personal use and to print and download material from this Website provided that you do not modify any content without our consent. You are also free to bookmark and share links directing others to content on this Website. Material on this Website must not otherwise be reproduced or republished, either online or offline, without prior written permission by ESL Power Systems, Inc.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy pertains to the use of this Website. ESL Power Systems, Inc. values your privacy.
Links to Other Websites This Website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of that we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any Website other than our own.
Registration and Use of Personal Information Registration is not required in order to use or access this Website. However, this site may make forums, blogs, message boards or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or provide articles. If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent. Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels. This Website may collect your name and email address if you leave a comment, or subscribe to our mailing list. In providing this information you consent for it to be used for these purposes. We will not provide this information to any other party.
Legal Disclaimer We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on this Website.
Visitor Conduct
With the exception of personally identifiable information, the use of which is covered under the Privacy Policy section, ESL Power Systems, Inc. reserves the right to modify or withdraw posts to this Website.
When using this Website you shall not post or send to or from this Website any material:
for which you have not obtained all necessary consents;
that is discriminatory, obscene, pornographic, defamatory, liable to incite racial hatred, in breach of confidentiality or privacy, which may cause annoyance or inconvenience to others, which encourages or constitutes conduct that would be deemed a criminal offence, give rise to a civil liability, or otherwise is contrary to the law; or
which is harmful in nature including, and without limitation, computer viruses, Trojan horses, corrupted data, or other potentially harmful software or data.
By posting content to this Website, you warrant and represent that you either own or otherwise control all of the rights to that content, including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the content, or that your use of the content is a protected fair use.
You agree to indemnify and hold us and our affiliated companies, and their directors, officers and employees, harmless for any and all claims or demands, including reasonable attorney fees that arise from or otherwise relate to your use of this Website, any content you supply to this Website, or your violation of these Terms or the rights of another.
Contact Details
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone, email, or postal mail, our contact information is as follows:
webmaster@eslpwr.com
ESL Power Systems, Inc.
2800 Palisades Drive Corona, CA 92880
+1 (951) 739-7020
This privacy policy was last updated on August 10, 2012.
Contact: ESL Power Systems, Inc.2800 Palisades Drive | Corona, CA 92878-9427t: (800) 922-4188 | +1 (951) 739-7000 | e: info@eslpwr.com
Follow:
Have a Question?
To receive additional information on ESL’s products or services fill out our request information form here.
